<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "/SysSchema/dita/dtd/technicalContent/dtd/topic.dtd">
<topic xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" base="base" id="dynamic_partitioning_deep" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Dynamic Partitioning</title>

  <body>
    <note audience="MSCCInternal"><p>Content sourced from Saratoga Device
    Specification - Issue 12</p></note>

    <p>Switchtec introduces a unique partitioning scheme which provides a
    controlled mapping layer that allows for dynamic mapping of physical ports
    to P2P bridge functions. This scheme makes the relationship of physical
    ports and switch P2P bridges not 1:1. There can be far more switch P2P
    bridges than physical ports allowing switchtec to present P2P bridges to
    the host that are not mapped to physical ports.</p>

    <p>This mapping layer allows for dynamic migration of physical ports
    between active partitions, and provides the following features:</p>

    <ul>
      <li><p> Hosts in each partition configure the switch to support all
      potential targets on physical ports.</p></li>

      <li><p> Migrating ports between partitions are supported natively with
      no OS, BIOS or driver modifications.</p></li>

      <li><p> Migrating ports appear as hot-add and hot-remove events.
      </p></li>
    </ul>

    <p><xref href="#dynamic_partitioning_deep/fig_Switchtec_Dynamic_Partitioning_2ihi9frg9">
    </xref> illustrates the Switchtec implementation of dynamic partitioning
    where there are a total of 5 physical ports and two hosts. In this
    example, each host (orange and green) is able to see 5 P2P bridges but the
    orange host only has two Endpoints attached while the green host only has
    three Endpoints attached. MRPC can be used to dynamically shift physical
    ports (PCIe SSDs in this example) between hosts without having to reboot
    the hosts.</p>

    <note audience="MSCCInternal"><p>Source graphics: <xref href="http://bby1dms01.pmc-sierra.internal/DocMgmt/fileinfo.cfm?file_id=437731" scope="external">http://bby1dms01.pmc-sierra.internal/DocMgmt/fileinfo.cfm?file_id=437731</xref>
    (Page-5)</p></note>

    <fig id="fig_Switchtec_Dynamic_Partitioning_2ihi9frg9">
      <title>Switchtec Dynamic Partitioning</title>

      <image href="dynamic_partitioning_logical_to_physical.svg" width="5in"/>
    </fig>

    <p>When referring to logical P2Ps, Switchtec makes two unique
    distinctions:</p>

    <ul>
      <li><p>Normal P2P Bridge - This is a P2P that is bound to a real
      physical port on the switch and appears as an empty slot to the host if
      no EP is connected to the port</p></li>

      <li><p>Shadow P2P Bridge - This is a P2P that is unbound to a physical
      port on the switch and appears as an empty slot to the host</p></li>
    </ul>
  </body>
</topic>