<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?workdir /C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\temp\temp20181123111806622\Other?><?workdir-uri file:/C:/Git/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/DITA-OT1.8.5/temp/temp20181123111806622/Other/?><?path2project ..\?><?path2project-uri ../?><topic xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" id="Abstract_4iu8j35d2" xml:lang="en-US" ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)                             (topic ut-d)                             (topic indexing-d)                            (topic hazard-d)                            (topic abbrev-d)                            (topic pr-d)                             (topic sw-d)                            (topic ui-d)                            (topic struct-d)                            (topic firmware-d)                            (topic pmcrevhis-d)                            a(props  sp-version)                            a(props  pmc_switch)                            a(props   pmc_package)                            a(props   pmc_phy)                            a(props   ddr-width)                            a(props   package)                            a(props   fw_package)                            a(props   pcie-drive-ports )                            a(props   pcie-host-ports)                            a(props   raid-support )                            a(props   sas-ports )                             a(props   media)                            a(props   component)   " class="- topic/topic " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="topic:1;2:112">
  <title class="- topic/title " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="title:1;3:10">Abstract</title>

  <body class="- topic/body " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="body:1;5:9">
    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="p:1;6:8">The Segmentation and Re-assembly (SAR / OPSA) subsystem components
    perform rate capture and recovery, and ODUk segmentation and reassembly
    operations for OTN data transmitted and received over the Interlaken
    interface.</p>

    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="p:2;11:8">The OPSA components performs the rate capture and recovery functions,
    supporting an aggregate 600G of bandwidth and up to 190 independent
    traffic streams. The ingress rate is captured via ingress receive clock
    information from the SERDES and from justification control information
    received in the ODUk overhead. This enables rate capture of ingress OTUks
    from SERDES interfaces, demuxed ingress ODUks, ingress clients from SERDES
    interfaces, and clients demapped from ODUks. The OPSA components also
    recover/generate the egress rate, enabling timing control of egress
    OTUks/clients to SERDES interfaces. Timing control is also supported for
    egress muxed ODUks and clients mapped to ODUks.</p>

    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="p:3;22:8">Ingress rate capture and egress rate recovery PLL segments can be
    cascaded together to complete the rate adaptation functions required to
    fulfill the network operations defined in standards while meeting
    associated jitter and wander specifications.</p>

    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Abstract_4iu8j35d2.xml" xtrc="p:4;27:8">The SAR components are responsible for the segmentation and reassembly
    of switched ODUk packets as defined by the OIF-OFP Implementation
    agreement. The standard defines the rate capture parameters used to encode
    the rate of ODUks in-band in the size of the packets transported across
    the switch fabric. Definition of the rate capture parameters for various
    rate ODUks permits interoperability of the ODUk packet streams segmented
    at the fabric ingress and reassembled at the fabric egress. The SAR
    components also support insertion of the OIF-OFP SAR header at the fabric
    ingress and processing and removal of the header at the SAR egress. The
    SAR header timestamp field is used to enable latency compensation of
    switched ODUk packet streams.</p>
  </body>
</topic>