<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?workdir /C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\temp\temp20181123111806622\Other?><?workdir-uri file:/C:/Git/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/DITA-OT1.8.5/temp/temp20181123111806622/Other/?><?path2project ..\?><?path2project-uri ../?><topic xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" id="COPI_G5_Abstract_4iufyszha" xml:lang="en-US" ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)                             (topic ut-d)                             (topic indexing-d)                            (topic hazard-d)                            (topic abbrev-d)                            (topic pr-d)                             (topic sw-d)                            (topic ui-d)                            (topic struct-d)                            (topic firmware-d)                            (topic pmcrevhis-d)                            a(props  sp-version)                            a(props  pmc_switch)                            a(props   pmc_package)                            a(props   pmc_phy)                            a(props   ddr-width)                            a(props   package)                            a(props   fw_package)                            a(props   pcie-drive-ports )                            a(props   pcie-host-ports)                            a(props   raid-support )                            a(props   sas-ports )                             a(props   media)                            a(props   component)   " class="- topic/topic " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\COPI_G5_Abstract_4iufyszha.xml" xtrc="topic:1;2:120">
  <title class="- topic/title " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\COPI_G5_Abstract_4iufyszha.xml" xtrc="title:1;3:10">COPI Abstract</title>

  <body class="- topic/body " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\COPI_G5_Abstract_4iufyszha.xml" xtrc="body:1;5:9">
    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\COPI_G5_Abstract_4iufyszha.xml" xtrc="p:1;6:8">The Combined OTN and Packet Interface (COPI) provides Interlaken
    interfaces to transfer client data between the Central Packet Buffer
    (DCPB) and peer Interlaken devices. The COPI operates on a mix of up to
    190 channels of OTN and packet traffic (of which up to 120 channels can
    carry packet traffic) carried to and from the DCPB. The COPI operates
    either in 1x500G mode with a single Interlaken interface or in 3x200G mode
    with three Interlaken interfaces. A third mode, 1x600G, is available for a
    single Interlaken channel for PIF traffic only. The COPI transmit (fabric
    ingress) path performs burst validation, channel ID remapping, and header
    insertion before sending traffic to the Interlaken interfaces. The COPI
    receive (fabric egress) path accepts data from the Interlaken interfaces
    and performs burst validation, channel filtering, channel ID remapping and
    header extraction. The Interlaken interfaces transfer packets in segments
    or bursts with in-band flow control, and support 25.78125 Gbps / 28.125
    Gbps / 53.125 Gbps / 56.25 Gbps rates. The COPI integrates the ITS_PKT500
    block which provides up to 500G of test packet generation and monitoring
    over 120 channels. The COPI can be configured to merge the generated test
    traffic with the receive datapath toward the DCPB or else merge with the
    transmit datapath coming out of the DCPB toward the Interlaken interfaces.
    The COPI can be configured to monitor test traffic received or transmitted
    between the DCPB and Interlaken interfaces. The COPI can also measure OTN
    packet traffic datapath latency on the receive path before sending the
    packets to the DCPB.</p>
  </body>
</topic>