<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?workdir /C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\temp\temp20181123111806622\Other?><?workdir-uri file:/C:/Git/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/DITA-OT1.8.5/temp/temp20181123111806622/Other/?><?path2project ..\?><?path2project-uri ../?><topic xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" id="Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83" xml:lang="en-US" ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)                             (topic ut-d)                             (topic indexing-d)                            (topic hazard-d)                            (topic abbrev-d)                            (topic pr-d)                             (topic sw-d)                            (topic ui-d)                            (topic struct-d)                            (topic firmware-d)                            (topic pmcrevhis-d)                            a(props  sp-version)                            a(props  pmc_switch)                            a(props   pmc_package)                            a(props   pmc_phy)                            a(props   ddr-width)                            a(props   package)                            a(props   fw_package)                            a(props   pcie-drive-ports )                            a(props   pcie-host-ports)                            a(props   raid-support )                            a(props   sas-ports )                             a(props   media)                            a(props   component)   " class="- topic/topic " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="topic:1;2:138">
  <title class="- topic/title " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="title:1;3:10">Insert Path Shared Buffer Features</title>

  <body class="- topic/body " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="body:1;5:9">
    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="p:1;6:8">The GCC Processor insertion Shared Packet Buffer holds all Packet Data
    Unit (PDU) after all Ethernet headers and FCS have been removed. The
    Shared Packet Buffer is sized for 12 active ODUC1 or OTU4 GCC Links,
    327680 bytes. The buffer is broken up into 512 byte blocks; 640 total
    blocks available. The Shared Packet Buffer fills one packet at a time and
    the GCC interface requires two bytes at a time for each GCC Link. A
    dropped packet interrupt occurs if there are not enough blocks for a full
    sized HDLC PDU (1968 bytes) as a new SOP arrives. This equates to four
    512-byte blocks. A 32-bit dropped packet count (saturates at 0x80000000)
    is available.</p>

    <p audience="DIGIG5_ROW" class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="p:2;17:30">The Shared Packet buffer output can support
    unicast (i.e each packet is destined to 1 GCC link) or multicast (i.e.
    each packet is destined to multiple GCC links). Multicast limit is upto 32
    unique GCC links. GCC link to link mapping number is configured by
    Software. For multicast multiple GCC links will have the same link mapping
    number configuration. The Hardware will do the appropriate routing of
    incoming link mapping number to GCC link based on this configuration.</p>

    <p audience="MSCCInternal" class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="p:3;25:32">Firmware manages the block descriptors for
    unicast and multicast every 200 <ph otherprops="symbolfont" class="- topic/ph " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Insert_Path_Shared_Buffer_Features_ghorj1i83.xml" xtrc="ph:1;26:65">µ</ph>s.
    Firmware writes a list of available blocks to an Empty FIFO which are used
    in order as each HDLC PDU arrives from the Ethernet interface. The used
    packet descriptors are written to a FIFO available to firmware which reads
    the descriptor and writes the descriptor to channelized queues. The
    descriptor is written to multiple queues in the case the Group Number is
    multicast to many GCC Links. A Group Number may multicast from 1:N where N
    = 1 to 32. Each queue is associated to a GCC Link and space for 32
    descriptors are assigned to the queue per the link's ODU2 rate multiple.
    Completed descriptors from the queue are written to a Freed FIFO. Firmware
    reads the Freed FIFO and determines when the blocks are free. When free,
    the block number is written back into the Empty FIFO. HDLC processing is
    performed after the packet data is read from the buffer.</p>
  </body>
</topic>