<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?workdir /C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\temp\temp20181123111806622\Other?><?workdir-uri file:/C:/Git/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/DITA-OT1.8.5/temp/temp20181123111806622/Other/?><?path2project ..\?><?path2project-uri ../?><topic xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" id="ITS_PKT500_Overview_6iu82jf1j" xml:lang="en-US" ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)                             (topic ut-d)                             (topic indexing-d)                            (topic hazard-d)                            (topic abbrev-d)                            (topic pr-d)                             (topic sw-d)                            (topic ui-d)                            (topic struct-d)                            (topic firmware-d)                            (topic pmcrevhis-d)                            a(props  sp-version)                            a(props  pmc_switch)                            a(props   pmc_package)                            a(props   pmc_phy)                            a(props   ddr-width)                            a(props   package)                            a(props   fw_package)                            a(props   pcie-drive-ports )                            a(props   pcie-host-ports)                            a(props   raid-support )                            a(props   sas-ports )                             a(props   media)                            a(props   component)   " class="- topic/topic " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\ITS_PKT500_Overview_6iu82jf1j.xml" xtrc="topic:1;2:123">
  <title class="- topic/title " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\ITS_PKT500_Overview_6iu82jf1j.xml" xtrc="title:1;3:10">ITS_PKT500 Overview</title>

  <body class="- topic/body " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\ITS_PKT500_Overview_6iu82jf1j.xml" xtrc="body:1;5:9">
    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\ITS_PKT500_Overview_6iu82jf1j.xml" xtrc="p:1;6:8">The Integrated Test Set 500G Packet Tester (ITS_PKT500) generates and
    monitors up to 500 Gbps of packet traffic carried over up to 120 channels.
    The ITS_PKT500 generates packets with programmable payloads and
    programmable sequences of packet lengths for each channel. Each generated
    channel can be configured to include optional packet overhead fields
    including an incrementing packet sequence number for packet order
    validation, a timestamp for path latency testing, and a static field per
    channel for channel differentiation. The generator inserts an optional FCS
    over a selected portion of the payload to enable data validation. The
    ITS_PKT500 monitors each channel as it checks the packet sequence fields
    for continuity, checks the static field against the expected value, and
    checks the FCS in the packet against its own FCS calculated over the
    selected portion of the payload. The packet monitor can extract the
    timestamp from a selected channel and compare it to the internal timestamp
    counter to calculate end to end path latency for the channel. The packet
    generators and monitors provide per channel counters and interrupts for
    packets and bytes sent and received, and for flow control status and data
    errors detected in the monitor. The ITS_PKT500 uses channelized XOFF flow
    control backpressure, and channel level credit-based rate limiters to
    produce controlled channel data rate profiles.</p>
  </body>
</topic>