<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?workdir /C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\temp\temp20181123111806622\Other?><?workdir-uri file:/C:/Git/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/XDocs-DITA-OT-185/DITA-OT1.8.5/temp/temp20181123111806622/Other/?><?path2project ..\?><?path2project-uri ../?><topic xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" id="Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k" xml:lang="en-US" ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)                             (topic ut-d)                             (topic indexing-d)                            (topic hazard-d)                            (topic abbrev-d)                            (topic pr-d)                             (topic sw-d)                            (topic ui-d)                            (topic struct-d)                            (topic firmware-d)                            (topic pmcrevhis-d)                            a(props  sp-version)                            a(props  pmc_switch)                            a(props   pmc_package)                            a(props   pmc_phy)                            a(props   ddr-width)                            a(props   package)                            a(props   fw_package)                            a(props   pcie-drive-ports )                            a(props   pcie-host-ports)                            a(props   raid-support )                            a(props   sas-ports )                             a(props   media)                            a(props   component)   " class="- topic/topic " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k.xml" xtrc="topic:1;2:121">
  <title class="- topic/title " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k.xml" xtrc="title:1;3:10">Timestamp Counter</title>

  <body class="- topic/body " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k.xml" xtrc="body:1;5:9">
    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k.xml" xtrc="p:1;6:8">The timestamp counter is a free running counter based on the system
    reference clock. The counter output is used to provide the timestamps that
    may be inserted in the packet by the packet assembler. The counter output
    is also available to the test packet monitor where it can be compared to
    the timestamp that was inserted into the packet by an upstream packet
    assembler to determine the total path latency.</p>

    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k.xml" xtrc="p:2;13:8">If the upstream packet assembler is in another device, then the
    timestamp counters must be synchronized across the devices to provide a
    meaningful comparison. The timestamp counter can synchronize to the device
    frame pulse input, the PMON synchronization input, or the time-of-day one
    pulse-per-second input or output signals. The timestamp counter can select
    one of these device signals to align the counter roll-over to. When the
    selected signal has a rising edge, if the counter is not within a
    tolerance window of rolling over, it is reset to 0. Interrupt bits are
    provided to indicate whenever the selected counter synchronization source
    has had an event, and whenever the counter re-synchronizes to the
    source.</p>

    <p class="- topic/p " xtrf="C:\Git\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\XDocs-DITA-OT-185\DITA-OT1.8.5\samples\digi\Other\Timestamp_Counter_niu82jf1k.xml" xtrc="p:3;25:8">The timestamp counter, packet generator timestamp insertion, and packet
    monitor latency calculator use a 32-bit field for the timestamp. The
    roll-over value for the timestamp counter and latency calculator is
    programmable. The timestamp counter can be programmed to the same period
    as the synchronization source input to prevent undesired repeated
    re-synchronizations. Alternatively, the timestamp counter can be
    configured to synchronize once to the selected input source and then
    free-run.</p>
  </body>
</topic>